Guide to the Stanford University Print Collection SC1039
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University print collection
1862-2001
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Mullgardt, Louis Christian
Stanford, Leland
Chagoya, Enrique
Oliveira, Nathan
Olmsted, Frederick Law
Paoletti, Antonio.
SC1039
354 item(s)
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Materials were acquired through varied sources.
Information about Access
Access: Materials are open to research use.
Scope and Contents note
This collection contains lithographs, drawings, watercolor paintings, art prints, diplomas, certificates, printed illustrations, cartoons, advertisements, bird's eye maps, and other printed formats. The main focus is Stanford University and its founders; subjects include the career of Leland Stanford, his racing horses, Stanford University's history, student life, campus buildings, views of campus, faculty achievements, and others. Some items of note include The Leland Stanford Junior University, Plan of Central Premises, 1888, by Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, architects, and Frederick Law and J. C. Olmsted, landscape architects; original water color designs of mosaics for Memorial Church by A. E. Paoletti; nine demands posted by Students for a Democratic Society on the door of the President's office, concerning the Stanford Research Institute, 1968; original sketches by Leland Stanford, Jr.; Currier and Ives prints of Stanford's race horses; design for the president's house by Louis Christian Mullgardt, architect; woodblock prints by Della Taylor Hoss from Mary Curry Tressider's “Trees of Yosemite," 1932; print by Enrique Chagoya “Illegal Spirit in Black and White", 1994; caricature sketches of members of Beta Theta Pi, including Winstead “Doodles" Weaver, circa 1935; and Santa Fe Wing No. 9 by Nathan Oliveira, 1990.
Currier & Ives.; Mullgardt, Louis Christian; Stanford, Leland; Chagoya, Enrique; Oliveira, Nathan; Stanford, Jane Lathrop; Stanford University. Memorial Church; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Students.;; Stanford, Leland; Olmsted, Frederick Law; Paoletti, Antonio.; Paoletti, Antonio.
- Prints
  - Plan of the Leland Stanford Junior Univeristy, Palo Alto, California., P001; prints & a negative (Box C1)
    General note
    Bird's eye rendering of Quad
    Campus Plan; Shepley, Rutan, & Coolidge; Olmsted
  - Plan of the Leland Stanford Junior University, Palo Alto, California., P001; prints (Box MC)
    Contents: 1 item is copy on mylar; 1 item is trimmed, encapsulated & on mount; 1 item is from ACCN 2008-135
    Campus Plan; Shepley, Rutan, Coolidge, Olmsted
  - Plan for whole university differing from plan of Olmsted. Sketch shows two quads, the second east of the main quad with a central building similar to the 1919 library., P001a; black & white sketch; 14 x 45 (Box MC)
    in a mount
    Campus Plan; Bakewell and Brown
  - Sunol, P002; 10 1/2 x 14 (Box B1)
    Palo Alto Stock Farm - Horses; Boyd, H.
  - Electioneer by Rysdyk's Hambletonian, Dam Green Mountain Maid be Harry Clay. Property of Hon. Leland Stanford, Palo Alto Stock Farm., P003; 12 x 16 (Box B1)
    Palo Alto Stock Farm - Horses; Wyttenbach, E.
  - Electioneer, 125. Sired by Rysdyk's Hambletonian. Owned by Leland Stanford. Palo Alto Stock Farm. Menlo Park, California., P004; Lithograph; 22 x 28 (Box D1)
  - Palo Alto, 5353 sired by Electioneer, 125. First Dam: Dame Winnie, Thoroughbred. Owned by Leland Stanford. Palo Alto Stock Farm. Menlo Park, California., P005; lithograph; 22 x 28 (Box D1)
    Palo Alto Stock Farm - Horses
  - Assembly Hall. Suggestion for color. Plate 22. n.d., P006; watercolor; 11 x 17 (Box B1)
    Assembly Hall; Farmer, Edward M.
  - Cactus Garden., P007; watercolor; 10 x 14 (Box B1)
    Cactus Garden; Zeus, C.C.
  - Robles Adobe. The house built by Secundido Robles., P008; 14 x 24 (Box C1)
    Robles Adobe; Clark, A. B.; Clark, Arthur Bridgman
  - Frenchman's Tower on Page Mill Road, an etching from an early photograph., P009; etching; 10 x 15 (Box B1)
    Frenchman's tower; Coutts, Peter; Sanford, James
  - Escondito Cottage, P010; watercolor; 9 x 13 (Box B1)
    faculty housing; Coutts, Peter
  - The United States of America Panama-Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco, 1915. Celebrating the opening of the Panama Canal, the international jury of awards has conferred a silver medal upon Leland Stanford Junior University, Palo Alto, California, for pottery, in the Department of Education. Engraved and printed by the U.S. Bureau of Engraving and Printing., P011; 19 x 24 (Box D1)
    Education Department - 1915; Baldwin, M. W.
  - Assembly, California Legislature, 1964 (first extraordinary) Session. Resolution relative to commending Dr. Wallace Sterling, President of Stanford University., 1-Apr-64; P012; 12 x 20 (Box C1)
    Sterling, J. E. Wallace; Sterling, J. E. Wallace
  - Palo Alto and the Leland Stanford Junior University. Probably from the San Francisco News Letter. Three views of the artist's conception of what the campus would look like when completed., 1888; P013; 21 x 28 (Box D1)
    Jan 2006: matches top half of real estate promotion for Palo Alto put out by N. C. Carnall & Co. in 1888 [offered by Swann Galleries]
    Campus Plan; Peixotto
  - Birds-eye view of Mayfield, Leland Stanford Jr. University and Palo Alto, the University Town. Published by Carnall-Fitzhugh-Hopkins Co. Lithograph by Dakin Publishing Co., 1889; P014; lithograph; 24 x 37 (Box MC)
    Reproduction added from accn 2008-194
    Mayfield; Campus Plan - 1889
  - Leland Stanford Junior University Library and Assembly Hall. Percy and Hamilton Architects. Artist's conception of T. W. Stanford Library and assembly hall on Quad. Not as completed., 1898; P015; black and white sketch; 11 x 24 (Box D1)
    Percy and Hamilton; Library - Buildings - 1898; Assembly Hall
  - The Leland Stanford Junior University now in the course of completion. ..issued with the Christmas number, San Francisco News Letter, 1887. Lithhographed by Britton and Rey., P016.1; color sketch; 11 x 28 (Box D1)
    Stanford University -- History.
  - The Leland Stanford Junior University now in the course of completion. ..; Same as P016.1, 1889; P016.2; 19 x 27 (Box D1)
  - The Leland Stanford Junior University now in the course of completion. ..; Same as P016.1 & P016.2, 1890; P016.3; 19 x 24 (Box B1)
  - Stanford Stadium. Sketch from an air view of stadium looking toward quad. Text gives specifications of new stadium. Framed print: (94-170), 21 x 18 1/4 inches (image is 11 x 14 in.) at SAL., 1922; P017; 23 x 16 1/2 (Box C1)
    Clark, A. B.; Stadium; Clark, Arthur Bridgman
  - Stanford University. Air view of campus by F. Standish, copyright 1930 by Stanley Milne., P018; photocopied painting; 12 x 19 (Box B1)
    campus views; Standish, F.
  - Stanford University of the present and of the immediate future. From an airplane photograph, copyright 1922 by Burton Crandall. Verso contains a plan of the campus locating the existing and proposed buildings. Attached is a 5 page pamphlet which appears to be directed at raising funds., P019 (Box C1)
    1 copy of print only is encapsulated
    Campus Plan - 1922
  - Stanford Scenes. No date, imprint, or further identification given. Color photographs of campus views. Contents: Hoover Tower, Memorial Church interior, Memorial Church exterior, Encina Hall & Hoover Tower, Memorial Church mosaics, Stanford Union, East Clock Tower, Memorial Hall, Physics Corner, West Gate Inner Quadrangle., P020; 10 x 13, in folder (Box A1)
    campus views
  - Frenchman's Tower on Page Mill Road, an etching by James Sanford from an early photograph. Includes copy of a Christmas card made from the same etching., P009; 10 x 15 (Box C1)
  - Stanford in Color. Ten views of Stanford in color. Photographed, lithographed, and published by Stanford University Press. Contents: Hoover Tower, Memorial Hall, University Library, Education Building, Stanford Union, East Clock Tower, Memorial Church, Archway to Memorial Court, Physics Corner, Museum. Descriptive pamphlet by Virginia L. Hobbs., P021; 10 x 13, in folder (Box A1)
    Contents: 3rd copy from accn 2000-309, no booklet; 4th copy from 2005-200; 5th and 6th copy from Accn 2017-089.
  - Ray Lyman Wilbur, President, Stanford University, January 1, 1916 to January 1, 1942. Copy of a painting by Hubbell., P022 (Box B1)
    Wilbur, Ray Lyman.; Hubbell
  - Lemos, Pedro J. Stanford etchings to Timothy Hopkins in appreciation. Contents: Stanford University Arch, "From the Foothills to the Bay," Memorial Court, The East Arch, Curving Roads at Stanford & Stanford Palms (same image). Also includes a short biography on Lemos and a letter of appreciation, "To Timothy Hopkins...", 30-Mar-21; P023; 11 x 15.5 in (Box B1)
    5/2001 letter not in folder
    campus views; Lemos, Pedro J.; Lemos, Pedro J. (Pedro Joseph), 1882-1954
  - Lemos, Pedro J. Stanford Scenes. 4 original pieces, rest are printed pieces (mostly from publications)., P024; various (Box A1)
    One original item is not signed.
    Lemos, Pedro J.; campus views; Lemos, Pedro J. (Pedro Joseph), 1882-1954
  - Stoll, John T.E. A portfolio of Stanford University, drawn and published by John T.E. Stoll. Contents: The new Stanford Union, th tower of the new eating hall, main entrance to the library, a wing of the new dormitory, the Memorial Church, the northwest entrance to Toyon, the basketball pavilion, a typical Stanford courtyard - Toyon Hall, Stanford's art gallery, interior of Toyon Hall, a Stanford Archway, an entrance to Toyon Hall., 1923; P025; 6 x 8 (Box B1)
    c. 12 from 2007-327
    Stoll, John T.E.; campus views; Stoll, John T.E.
  - The Leland Stanford Junior University; Plan of Central Premises, 1888, by Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge, architects, and Frederick Law and J. C. Olmsted, landscape architects. Includes: letter of tranmittal and copy, small note in envelope, and a note and a card recording contents (not necessarily accurate). In a large leather and satin book/ protective casing., 1888, 1937; P026 (Box C1)
    see also Map 237 for mylar reproduction
    Campus Plan - 1888; Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge; Coolidge, Charles A.; Olmsted, J.C. & Frederick Law;; Shepley, Rutan, Coolidge, Olmsted
  - Stern, Alec. Stanford Chapel., P028; etching (Box B2)
    Memorial Church; Stern, Alec
  - Lites, Arthur. Inner Quad viewing east or west gate. Print of a watercolor., 1932; P029; 8 x 10 (Box B2)
    Inner Quad; Lites, Arthur
  - Watercolors of Stanford Scenes reprinted from the Stanford Chapparal. Contents: the library, the farm, the Quad, the museum, and 2 copies of the west arch., June, 1938; P030 (Box A1)
    campus views; Stoll, John
  - Sketches for Stanford Milestones. Presented to Stanford University by Mr. and Mrs. Arthrur P. Lites. Contents: Inner Quad, Memorial Church, Library, Toyon, Frost Amphitheater, School of Education., P031; 4 x 7, mounted in pamphlet form (Box B2)
    campus views; Lites, Charlotte; Lites, Charlotte
  - "Warning! No shooting or trespassing allowed on these premises. The law will be strictly enforced. Jane L. Stanford.", P032; 11 x 16 (Box B2)
  - Mrs. Stanford to the women of Stanford University, April 22, 1903. Caligraphy by W. R. Briggs, 1914, with illuminations. (Formerly framed and hung in the Women's Clubhouse.), P033; ink & paint on vellum (?); 16 x 22 (Box C1)
    Missing - 4/95; found 06/2002
    Briggs, W. R.
  - Culver, Richard Keith. Miscellaneous drawings and papers. Contents: 2 copies "A College Calendar...;" 1 copy each of: self-portrait caricature, cartoon for Big Game 1895, cartoon of writer, and membership certificate for the Delta Upsilon Fraternity., circa 1895; P034 (Box B2)
    Big Game; Delta Upsilon Fraternity; Culver, Richard; Culver, Richard Keith
  - "Welcome to our Western Seat of Learning; no worthier lecturer has ever entered its walls." From the City Argus. Depicts Leland Stanford greeting former U.S. president Benjamin Harrison in front of the Quad, P035 (Box C1)
    Stanford, Leland - cartoons about
  - The doors thrown open. Drawn by Saalburg, printed by L. Schmidt & Lithograph Co. Under title Mr. Stanford is quoted as saying, "It is all for you my boy, and for the coming generations. My ambition is now satisfied. I have less desire to be president than to be the founder of an institution that will make presidents!", 1891?; P036 (Box C1)
    Stanford, Leland - cartoons about; Saalburg
  - California's best friend, drawn by H. Boyd, from the CIty Argus. Depicts Mr. Stanford shaking hands with Miss California, background shows Stanford's contributions to the state., P037 (Box C1)
    Stanford, Leland - cartoons about; Politics; Boyd, H.
  - California's representative man, Hon. Leland Stanford. From the City Argus., P038; 20 x 13 (Box C1)
    Politics; Stanford, Leland - cartoons about
  - No title. Depicts an unidentified man offering the Presidential chair to Leland Stanford. [San Francisco] City Argus., 1888; P039 (Box C1)
  - The Stanford Memorial Kindergartens. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper. Exterior and interior views of school no. 1., March 28, 1885; P040 (Box B2)
    Stanford Memorial Kindergartens; Leslie, Frank
  - Undergraduate library. Preliminary sketches of the floor plan of the undergraduate library by John Earle Warnecke and Associates., P041 (Box MC)
    Libraries; Warnecke, John Earle & Assoc.
  - Salviati and Company. Mosaic decoration in apse and above windows of Memorial Church, views of various mosaics created by Salviati and Company. Some signed by Jane L. Stanford., P042 (Box Own box)
    Scope and Contents note
    Box 1 Watercolor paintings: 42.40 Watercolor in two panels: host of angels and angels with cross and crown of thorns. With Jane L. Stanford's approval on verso, 1900 42.41 Watercolor in two panels: angels with crown and host of angels 42.42 Watercolor of Christ's arrival in Heaven (with blank spaces for arches). Signed by A. Erm. Paoletti 42.43 Watercolor of Christ on throne in Heaven under rainbow (with blank spaces for arches). Signed by A. Erm. Paoletti 42.44 Three types of mosaic stone and when to use them, on black background board 42.45 Photograph of a mosaic, many panels including angels, Christ, cherubs, children with lamb. Signed note by Jane L. Stanford on verso, 1900 42.46 Watercolor of Adam and Eve in Garden with God. Signed by A. Erm. Paoletti 42.47 Watercolor of prophets under scene of Christ-child and Satan being cast out of Heaven. Signed by A. Erm. Paoletti 42.48 Two panels: young Mother Nature floating above clouds and young Father Time also floating. With Jane L. Stanford's approval on verso, 1901 42.49 Black and white watercolor of Christ and followers, front of Memorial Church 42.50 Mosaics over 4 arches: “alpha," “miracle of Moses," “harp of David," “omega," over Bible scenes 42.51 Mosaics over 4 arches: “peace," “religion," “mother's love," over virtues and Bible scenes 42.52 “Original color sketch for mosaic on front of Stanford Memorial Church" (color of 42.49)
    Box 2 Prints and photographs: 42.1 Christ with halo and book 42.2 Christ crucified, carried by angels 42.3 Christ comforting afflicted 42.4 Christ visits “the widow" 42.5 Resurrection of Saint Lazarus 42.6 Christ crucified with emblems and evangelists 42.7 Father, Son, and Holy Ghost, worshipped by 2 angels 42.8 Pious IX grave 42.9 “Our Lord in Glory" 42.10 “Marriage of Our Lady" 42.11 “The Resurrection" 42.12 “Plafond of the Foyet of the Opera House" 42.13 Preacher saying mass under Christ and heavenly host (3 copies) 42.14 Mosaic of a woman's face - two different sizes of pieces (I and II ere Categorie A) 42.15 Mosaic of a woman's face - two different sizes of pieces (III and IV eme Categorie A) 42.16 Mosaic of a young Christ - two different sizes of pieces (I ere and II eme Categorie B) 42.17 Same as 42.16 with one side in color 42.18 Mosaic of young Christ (III eme Categorie B) and mosaic of detail (I ere Categorie) 42.19 Mosaic of Virgin Mary and different sizes of stones and when to use them 42.20 Woman with shall and purse, in flowered frame 42.21 Woman holding a jug with another on her head, in flowered frame 42.22 Woman in wrap standing by a fire 42.23 Resurrected Christ with eyes and hands upturned, in frame 42.24 Three scenes: plant life, boats with seagulls over them, and boats on a lake 42.25 Archer-woman wearing skirt and crushing grapes for wine, with dog 42.26 Woman with wrap bathing in waterfall under tree branch 42.27 Angel in robe 42.28 Christ with chalice 42.29 “Birth of Our Lord" 42.30 “Our Lord ascending into Heaven" 42.31 Maiden in flowing gown, carrying branches with blossoms and two doves 42.32 The last supper with Christ making sign of peace 42.33 Woman in shawl and head-covering, in flowered frame 42.34 Triangular picture of maiden, children, and animals in bower 42.35 Last supper with Christ breaking bread 42.36 Three panels: flowers, Christ with halo, and dark flowers under light flowers 42.37 Three panels: woman playing lute with two women reading, nude women dancing, and flowers 42.38 Three panels: berries, flowers, and leaves (pattern of four) 42.39 Woman with tambourine in flowered frame 42.53 Mosaic decoration in apse of the Leland Stanford Memorial Church Palo Alto California. Executed by Salviati and Co., Venice 1901. Photo mounted on linen. 42.54 Aurora di Guido Reni. Color print. “Approved for the outside of the Memorial Church at Stanford University. Rome Italy Dec. 18th 1900 Jane L. Stanford" 42.55 “Completion of the large picture on the front façade of Memorial Church. Accepted by Mrs. Stanford … July 27, 1904. Chas. Ed. Hodges, Archt." Black and white reproduction mounted on board with Salviati stamp. 42.55 Jacob's Dream 42.56 Moses charged to take Israel from Egypt 42.57 The blessing of Isaac 42.58 Joseph sold 42.59 Sacrifice of Abraham 42.60 Prophecy of the Prophets 42.61 Angel [one of the archangels] 42.62 Hymns of David 42.63 Glory of the Angels [celestial choir - figures facing right] 42.64 Glory of the Angels [celestial choir - figures facing left] 42.65 Jacob going to Canaan 42.66 Joshua, successor to Moses 42.67 Isaiah 42.68 Faith 42.69 Jeremiah [bears note and signature of Jane L. Stanford, Nov. 19, 1900] 42.70 Angel [bears note and signature of Jane L. Stanford, Nov. 19, 1900] 42.71 Elias [bears note and signature of Jane L. Stanford, Nov. 19, 1900] 42.72 David [bears note and signature of Jane L. Stanford, Nov. 19, 1900] 42.73 Angel [bears note and signature of Jane L. Stanford, Nov. 19, 1900] 42.74 - 42.88 Mosaics and designs used in other locations (London, Rome, New York, Berlin, Budapest) 42.89 - 42.98 Mosaics unidentified (Not used in Memorial Church)
    Memorial Church - mosaics; Paoletti, A. E.
  - A. Errmelao Paoletti and Salviati and Company. Drawings for mosaics of Memorial Church. Includes Aurora de Guido Reni., P042.53 (Box D1)
    See finding aid for full listing.
  - "Completion of the large picture on the front façade of Memorial Church. Accepted by Mrs. Stanford … July 27, 1904. Chas. Ed. Hodges, Archt." Black and white reproduction mounted on board with Salviati stamp, P042.55 (Box D1)
  - Peter Lassen's Bosquejo rancho patent signed by Abraham Lincoln. Includes a plot of the rancho's 22,000 acres. This rancho eventually became part of Leland Stanford's Vina Ranch., P044 (Box B2)
    Cat record prepared 3/26/08
    Vina Ranch - history
  - M'Guiness, Jim. Stanford red roofs. Watercolor print of campus buildings., 196?; P045 (Box B2)
    campus views; M'Guinness, Jim
  - Residence of Hon. Leland Stanford, at San Francisco., P046; colored lithograph; 5 1/2 x 8 1/4 (Box A1)
    Stanford San Francisco house
  - Sketches of arms and flags of schools of Stanford University, bo Prof. Eric Hutchinson. Sketches of arms, flags, and crests for Stanford University., 1967; P047
    Heraldic Banners; Hutchinson, Eric.
    - 10" x 7.5" sketch of flag (Law School); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 10" x 7.5" sketch of flag (Sch. of Medicine); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 10" x 7.5" sketch of flag (Sch. of Earth Sciences) (penultimate design); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 10" x 7.5" sketch of flag (Sch. of Earth Sciences); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 10" x 7.5" sketch of flag (Graduate School of Business); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 7.5"x10" black and white sketch of arms (Sch. of Education); b&w sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 7.5"x10" black and white sketch of arms (Sch. of Earth Sciences) (preliminary); b&w sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 7.5"x10" black and white sketch of arms (Sch. of Humanities and Sciences); b&w sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of arms (Law School); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of arms (Sch. of Engineering); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of arms (Graduate School of Business); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of arms (Sch. of Education); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of arms (Sch. of Humanities and Sciences); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of arms (Sch. of Earth Sciences); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 10" x 7.5" sketch of flag (Graduate Division); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 7.5"x10" black and white sketch of arms (Graduate Division); b&w sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of arms (Graduate Division); color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 7.5"x10" black and white sketch of Stanford University arms; b&w sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of Stanford University arms; color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 7.5"x10" sketch of Alumni Association arms; color sketch on cardboard (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 10"x8" photo of flag (Law School) (copy 1); photograph (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 10"x8" photo of flag (Law School) (copy 2); photograph (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Arms of the School of Medicine; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Arms of the School of Humanities & Sciences; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Arms of the School of Law; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Arms of the School of Engineering; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Arms of the Graduate School of Business; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Arms of the School of Earth Sciences; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Arms of the School of Education; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Arms of the Graduate Division; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 10"x8" photo of University flag; photograph (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Preliminary arms of the University; color sketch on cardboard (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Sketch of arms of the University; color sketch on cardboard (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Arms of the University; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - University seal flag; color sketch on cardboard (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 7"x7" photo of President's flag; photograph (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sketch of President's flag; color sketch on cardboard (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Arms of the President of the University; matted sketch and inscription (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - School of Engineering Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - School of Humanities and Sciences Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - School of Earth Sciences Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - School of Medicine Coat of Arms; matted sketch on cardboard (Box 4, Folder 4)